sendori.com 2010-01-02

# Sendori | Privacy Policy

| 

Sendori ("Sendori") values the privacy of our users, members, and others who use _[www.sendori.com](http://www.sendori.com/)_ (the "Sendori Service") (collectively or individually "Users"). This statement governs information you provide to us or that we learn from your use of the Sendori Service and tells you how we may collect, use, and in some instances share this information.

  1. **The Information Sendori Collects**

_User Provided Information_ :  You provide to Sendori what is generally called "personally identifiable" information ("PII") when you register as a domain owner or advertiser. 

In order to use this Web site, you must first complete the application form and create an account by providing an email and password. In addition, a security question and answer is collected for password recovery. Within the application you are required to give contact information such as name and email address. We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest. 

If approved, you must provide your full address and financial information such as PayPal or bank account information. The address and financial information is used to make and receive payments - i.e. we use Paypal to facilitate our order/payment processing. When you place an order you will be automatically transferred to Paypal's site. Please be aware that their privacy policy governs the use and collection of the information and is shared back with us to fulfill the order. PayPal is not currently integrated into the Sendori website, so all payments are handled manually. That is, we collect a PayPal address from our users, and use that address to send payments through the PayPal website. We also provide an email address which can be used to send payments to Sendori through PayPal. 

The Sendori Service is run using a hosting service. In addition, third-party domain parking companies are used to monetize Web visitors, not monetized by the Sendori Service. Sendori does not provide any personally identifiable information to any third-party domain parking companies. 

_" Cookies" Information_: When you visit the Sendori Service, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer. Sendori uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. Session based cookies are used for maintaining your login information, including your email and customer ID, after logging into the Sendori Service. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Sendori Service. By using these cookies, we can "remember" what you have done on the Sendori Service before and personalize our site for you. These persistent types of cookies can be removed, but each web browser is a little different, so please look through your browser "Help" file to learn the correct way to modify your cookies set-up. Please note that disabling cookies may prevent you from accessing some of the functionality and site offerings available via the Sendori Service. 

We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. 

_" Automatically Collected" Information_

: When you visit the Sendori Service or open one of our HTML emails, we may record certain information from your web browser by using different types of technology, including "clear gifs" or "web beacons". This "automatically collected" information may include your Internet Protocol address ("IP Address"), web browser type, the web pages or sites that you visit just before or just after the Sendori Service, the pages you view on our site, and the dates and times that you visit. These "clear gif" and "web beacons" are not tied to PII. 

  2. **The Way Sendori Uses Information**

Sendori uses the information that we collect to provide to you all of the features and services found on the Sendori Service, such as conversion tracking and conversion optimization. We will use your email address, without further consent, for non-marketing or administrative purposes such as notifying you of major site updates, or for User service. You may not opt-out of receiving these critical service update emails. 

Sendori uses all of the information that we collect from our Users to understand the usage trends and preferences, to improve the way the Sendori Service works and looks, to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, and to create new features and functionality.

Sendori uses automatically collected information and cookies information to: (a) remember your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Sendori Service; (b) provide custom, personalized advertisements, content, and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; and (d) monitor aggregate usage metrics such as total number of visitors and pages viewed. 

Sendori will not use your email address or other PII to send promotional or marketing messages without your consent. Your consent is given in the My Account area of the site. You will have the ability to opt-in as part of a specific future program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in. 

  3. **When Sendori May Disclose Information**

Sendori may disclose both personally identifiable and automatically collected information to affiliated companies or other businesses or persons to process such information on our behalf, to provide website maintenance and security, to offer certain features on the Sendori Service, to assist us in improving the way the Sendori Service works and looks, and to create new features. We will require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our Privacy Policy, we will use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information, and we will require these parties to use any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 

We may share automatically collected and other aggregate non-personally-identifiable information with interested third parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the Sendori Service. 

Except as otherwise noted in this Privacy Policy, Sendori does not share PII about Sendori Service users with third parties unless doing so is appropriate to carry out a user's request or it reasonably believes that doing so is legally required or is in Sendori's interest to protect its property or other legal rights or the rights or property of others.

We reserve the right to disclose your PII as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. 

We do not share User information with other third-party organizations for their marketing or promotional use without your consent 

or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in.

  4. **Member Profile and Password**

You have access to your PII and you may update, correct, or delete your member information and email subscription preferences at any time by going to the log-in section of the site.

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting User's member profile access. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times. 

  5. **Children**

Consistent with the federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request PII from anyone under the age of thirteen. Any person who provides their personal information to Sendori through the Sendori Service represents that they are 13 years of age or older. 

  6. **Our Commitment to Data Security**

No data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure security on our systems. We use secure server software (SSL) and firewalls to protect your information from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of such firewalls and secure server software. 

If Sendori learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. By using the Sendori Service or providing personal information to us you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of the Sendori Service. You may not opt out of receiving these emails. Sendori may post a notice on the Sendori Service if a security breach occurs. If this happens, you will need a web browser enabling you to view Sendori's Service. Sendori may also send an email to you at the email address you have provided to us in these circumstances. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify us via email at _[support@sendori.com](mailto:support@sendori.com)_.

  7. **Special Note to International Users**

The Sendori Service is hosted in the United States. If you are a User accessing the Sendori Service from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please note that you are transferring your personal data to the United States which does not have the same data protection laws as the EU and other regions, and by providing your personal data you consent to:

  * the use of your personal data for the uses identified above in accordance with the Privacy Policy; and

  * the transfer of your personal data to the United States as indicated above.

  8. **In the Event of Merger or Sale**

If Sendori should ever file for bankruptcy or have its assets sold to or merge with another entity, information Sendori receives from you through the Sendori Service is a Sendori asset and may be transferred. You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of your PII

  9. **Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy**

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the "effective date" on the Privacy Policy. For changes to this Privacy Policy that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of PII that you have provided to us, we will give you notice. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

  10. **Changes/Opt-Out**

We provide you the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having your PII used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase the service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on when you first login to your account, and on the My Account page. 

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at support@sendori.com. We offer an opportunity to opt-out of certain communications on our My Account page, or you may contact us at 650 380-4380, support@sendori.com or 555 12th Street, Suite 400, Oakland, CA 94607, to opt-out. 

  11. **Contacting Sendori**

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please email us at _[support@sendori.com](mailto:support@sendori.com)_.

Postal Mail Address: Sendori, Inc.

555 12th Street, Suite 400

Oakland, CA 94607

If you have a privacy concern regarding the Sendori Service or this Policy and if you cannot satisfactorily resolve it through the use of the Sendori Service you should write to: _[support@sendori.com](mailto:support@sendori.com)_. 

**Effective Date: February 28, 2007**

|
